Hi, Clark.
Lana.
I didn't think anybody else was out here.
Wow, looks like we had the same idea for cooling off.
Yeah, it's a scorcher.
You know, I'll come back.
No, why? It's a big lake.
There's enough room for both of us.
I'm game if you are.
No peeking.
Your turn, Clark.
Promise I won't peek.
Okay.
Clark?
Bill?
Don't do that.
Oh!
Oh, my God.
It's not funny.
I know.
I always said there should be nothing between us.
No, there's not.
Help!
What's wrong?
He's here.
Run.
Run!
No!
I made this whole world shine for you..
I dug holes.
I used my x-ray vision, but it's like she just vanished.
Was anybody else out there with you?
No.
Just me.
You were skinny dipping alone?
Well, I'm...
It was kind of a spur-of-the-moment kind of thing.
All right, son.
I'll give the sheriff a call.
Maybe I should skip school and go look for her.
Clark, it's not your responsibility to save everybody.
Besides, right now, we have a surprise for you.
Outside.
Wow, I didn't know you got a new truck.
Not mine, Clark.
It's yours.
What?
Oh, my God.
Wait till I tell Pete.
Hey, it's not just for fun, son.
We need a new truck around here anyway.
Well, how can we afford it?
Well, the extra money Lex gave us came in handy.
Considering the source, I'm surprised you used it.
Yeah, I know.
But I finally realized that I wasn't giving him a fair shake.
After all you've been through the last couple of months,
we're really happy to have you home.
I don't know what to say.
I would say that you will take...
Care of her?
I'll take good care of her.
Thanks.
All right.
Hey, you better get school.
You're late already.
Oh, if Sheriff Adams finds out anything about that girl,
we'll let you know.
Okay.
Hey, Clark.
Lana.
Look, about yesterday...
Oh, it's okay.
You're not mad?
About you running off?
No, I had a good view and you left.
So, who was screaming?
Some girl.
Was she okay?
I don't know.
She just kind of disappeared.
I'm really sorry I just left you. Again.
It's not like we had a date or anything.
But I had fun.
So did I.
Our relationship's always been about pain and angst.
I guess a little levity's refreshing.
Maybe after a while you'll stop torturing yourself
and realize that there's no reason why we shouldn't be together.
It's okay, Clark.
I'm willing to wait as long as you want.
Hey.
Hey, wait.
Hey, who are you?
What happened? I saw you get pulled into the ground.
At least tell me your name.
Uh, Sarah.
Sarah Conroy.
Okay, Sarah, what's going on?
He's after me.
Who?
He's always after me.
Well, I'm just trying to keep him from getting hurt.
Okay.
I'm going to let you talk to him.
No, it's fine.
And I'm going to let the only one I know
to go along with it.
Okay.
Let's go.
Clark.
Where were you?
Pete, did you see that guy?
What guy?
How could you miss him?
He had a big red cape on.
He was standing right there.
Sarah.
You must have...
Who's Sarah?
She was right there.
I need defense. It's working. I get it.
I'm not insane.
Well, what do you call skipping a history exam where 50% of your grade...
That's today?
That was today. You flunked.
Chloe, I need your help. Something came up at the lake yesterday.
Yeah, I heard.
You are referring to the Blue Lagoon moment with a certain former girlfriend, right?
You know about that?
Looks like this is high school. Everybody knows.
The only...
Did Sarah Conroy tell you?
Highly doubtful since I've never met anyone with that name.
Well, she's a new student, I think.
I saw her in the woods and I just saw her in the hallway.
She's definitely a candidate for Wallop. We would...
Well, that's too bad.
Since the Wall of Weird has been retired.
Chloe, who did this?
I did.
It's time to leave childish pursuits behind.
You're not the only one who grew up this summer.
Besides, I think the Daily Planet was beginning to frown on my little obsession.
But we know these stories are true.
Do we? People have died because of that wall.
And people have been saved, too.
I'm done chasing one Mills-Clark.
From now on, it's hard news that can be backed up with facts.
Like years ago, recorders, TV networks and achievers
have been ог much of gold VH.
Don't tell me you're smoothies.
Are you shouldering the message or I'll Goodnight?
Don't prolong things if they are so short.
Yourijk.
The fourth one is after you.
Anyway, this footer was taken out.
He's waiting for you.
L stomped on me.
Would you hand me that sword?
Is this new?
Depends on your definition.
It was a ceremonial weapon used by a group of 16th century samurai warriors.
The Kitai.
Ever heard of them?
Japanese history really isn't my strong suit.
Let me give you your first lesson.
Legend has it, this sword was forged in the fires of Mount Fuji.
The blade could cut through anything.
The Kitai never took it in the battle.
They never had to.
Until the day the strongest Kitai turned on his own.
One by one, the Kitai fell.
The sword fell at his hand.
Nothing left to lose.
The last of the Kitai lunged at the warrior with the sword.
The blade cut him clean in two.
But when the warrior's armor fell away,
the Kitai saw he wasn't even human.
They're just never- 계속 struggling with the siege in the
Works of Fotis.
Santa iba,
Cuando hayas chegado,
tu debest CarlaY si es tu que sueños,
Ele adolescents se latiráเสhis.
Table noصne beenJamal Ch Mateo Temporal.
You'll see Ray Rlya and Hannifl
I would have protected your secret. I would have protected you.
But I couldn't be trusted because I'm a Lutheran.
No, that's not it!
I don't care!
I'm going to dedicate myself to ensuring the whole world knows who Clark Kent really is.
Life as you know it is over.
Lex.
Lex!
Bob!
Dad, we got a big problem!
Sarah?
What are you doing here?
Lilacs.
I haven't seen lilacs in years.
My favorite. My mother used to grow them for me.
Where is your family?
Listen.
Please don't let him take me again.
Who?
The traveler, Clark.
How do you know my name?
No!
Sarah, you cannot escape.
No matter where you hide, I will always find you.
No!
Please!
Clark!
Thank God!
We've been so worried.
What happened?
You fell asleep while you were studying for your history exam.
It was a day and a half ago, son.
We've been trying to wake you ever since.
You must have been dreaming.
It was so real.
I met this girl, Sarah Conroy, and she was in trouble.
Conroy?
That's the name of our new next-door neighbor.
He has a teenage daughter.
They moved into Lana's old house?
There's been a moving truck there since yesterday.
How could I dream about...
About someone I've never even met?
Oh, no!
We weren't going to meet, were we?
It only got better, Mark.
I knew you were high.
But you just a little devilish.
I suppose.
Helly ho!
Well, I guess it's time.
Trust me.
I'll tell you if you will.
Tell me.
You've never met someone like this?
No.
Clark, have you been up all night?
I was kind of afraid to go to sleep.
I can't get over how real that dream was.
I feel like I should check on the Conroys.
What would you say to them, that Sarah
was in danger in your dreams?
You need to be careful, Clark.
I got to be careful when I'm sleeping, too.
You weren't just asleep, son.
You were out for 36 hours.
That just happens to coincide with that girl
moving in next door?
You think she's keeping me asleep?
I don't know, Clark.
But with all the weird things been going on around here,
you need to be careful.
So look, I'm asking you.
You stay away from the neighbors.
Missed you at school the last few days.
Haven't been feeling so good.
To be honest, you look a little tired.
Maybe you should try and get some sleep.
No.
I'll be fine.
OK.
Well.
Um, I brought you your homework.
Mr. Blair said that you could make up your history exam
as long as you have a note from your parents.
You're the best.
Can I tell you something?
Sure.
I had this dream, and it's really freaking me out.
What was it about?
A lot of things.
This girl.
Oh.
No, Lana, it's not like that.
She needed help.
Let me guess.
You had to save her.
Except I couldn't.
Her name's Sarah, and she moved into your old house.
When did you meet her?
That's the thing.
I haven't.
How could I be dreaming about her?
Well, maybe if you walked me through the dream,
we could figure it out together.
You don't think I'm nuts?
No.
Clark, I think you have a lot of issues,
but I do not think you have lost your mind.
OK, so where did you see her first?
Breda Lake.
You were there.
Really?
What were we doing?
Nothing.
It's really hazy.
OK.
Well, I have a better idea.
Why don't we go see Sarah in person?
No.
I'll tell little Carl at the car.
OK.
You know what.
She seems so bad.
Do the doctors think she'll come out of it?
No.
There's always hope.
It must be really hard to see your daughter like this.
Probably quite a lot.
Right.
Yeah.
Sarah's my niece.
So, this is your old house, Lana.
And you're the boyfriend next door.
What exactly happened?
Clark.
It's okay. It's no secret.
It was a car accident.
Sarah and her parents went off the low bridge on their way home from a soccer game.
Paramedics say Sarah was asleep, which is probably why she survived.
Sarah's from Smallville?
Granville. Just over the county line.
Bilacs. Those are Sarah's favorite.
Yes.
How did you know that?
They're my favorite, too.
Must be kismet, living in the same house.
That's an interesting medal.
This?
Well, it's just good old Saint Christopher.
The patron saint of travelers, right?
Yes. Yes, I say his prayer every night in the hopes that Sarah's journey will end and she'll come back to us.
Look, I'm sorry. You'll have to excuse me. It's time for Sarah's medication.
Thank you for stopping by.
I'm sure you'll be all right.
I'll be fine.
Dad, I thought I made it clear that I'm back, fully committed to Luthor Corp and to you.
And I'm delighted...
Do you hear it?
Now, what's the problem?
I've been blocked out of half the computer files I need to do my job.
Insufficient security clearance.
Thank you, Milly.
These, uh...
Security measures, Lex, are a necessary evil. You should know that.
We have to protect our assets.
From me?
I applaud your renewed commitment to Luther Corp.
After what you've been through, it's remarkable.
But you think I might betray you again.
Betray me? That's an interesting notion.
Might you?
I want this to work.
I want us to be a family again.
You have nothing to fear from me.
Why have you refused to complete the psychological profile?
Come on, Dad.
You've never believed in that psychobabble, and neither do I.
I believe that, uh, personal, emotional problems...
are bound to affect day-to-day decision-making.
I think that dreams can often reveal hidden dangers...
and that the world is in service of warning.
Spare me the Jungian cliff notes, Dad.
It's five sessions, Lex. That's all.
I thought you wanted to reestablish our bond.
I do.
Then do it.
Prove that my total confidence in you is justified.
Clark Kent dreaming of the girl next door.
Isn't it nice to know that some things never change?
Right now, I'm just trying to stay awake.
Yeah. Even Red Bull has its limits. Trust me.
I've tested them.
I think Sarah's reaching out to me for help.
Entering your dreams to communicate?
How else would I know these details of her life?
Like the lilacs?
There is a theory that telepathic receptivity is increased during REM sleep.
It has to do with frontal lobe activity.
My frontal lobe is acting as a beacon.
I've never seen a case this dramatic.
But we all know that your brain is wired a little differently than the rest of ours.
Add the fact that the river where she crashed is a known source for our favorite green stuff,
and you have the perfect Smallville cocktail for weirdness.
You think the meteor rocks gave her this ability?
Well, once she's in, she can keep you asleep.
It certainly explains the day-and-a-half snore-a-thon.
I didn't wake up until the traveler appeared.
And I think it's her uncle.
Or a manifestation of fear that she has for her uncle.
Sorry. Didn't mean to get all Freudian on you.
No.
Her uncle is all-powerful in her life.
Why wouldn't he be in her dreams?
You're not buying the altruism angle?
My faith in human kindness is not what it used to be.
You up for a trip to the courthouse to see what public records tell us about Uncle Nicholas?
I have a deadline for the Daily Planet.
And shockingly, a wall of weird story doesn't take precedence in their mind.
No time for childish pursuits anymore.
Hey, now that's not fair.
You know that if I had a choice, I would definitely be down there pulling dusty records with you.
I doubt that.
It's okay, I'll grab Lana.
Yeah, at least she can provide a constant source of caffeine.
Now I know why public records are public.
They're incredibly boring.
Not all of them.
Take a look at this.
Wow.
Sarah's parents were rich.
When they died, she inherited everything.
One guest was in control of the money.
Uncle Nicholas.
As long as she stays in a coma, he controls the wealth.
But he still hasn't done anything wrong.
I mean, taking care of your niece and living a nice life isn't exactly a smoking gun.
Then why is Sarah so scared of him?
I just don't get it.
Hey, you're tired.
I'm afraid to close my eyes.
Uncle put on another pot of coffee.
You don't have to stay.
I want to, Clark.
Sonny?
Father?
Come here, Cory.
Don't clean this room.
Mother?
No, hide her.
Don't you hear?
Move it in all the room.
That's his way of moving things.
That was fast.
Sarah.
Hi.
Must have fallen asleep.
Yeah.
How do you get into my dreams?
I don't know, Clark.
This has never happened to me before.
I mean, just the other day, suddenly I was in the woods,
and then at school, and then at your house.
I realized what happened when you and Lana came to see me.
You can hear us?
Yeah.
It's like being in a long, dark tunnel.
I mean, sometimes it's open, but sometimes it's not.
I tried to reach out to you.
I mean, you don't know what it's like to be locked in your own body.
Never any contact.
Sarah, who's the traveler?
Oh, we shouldn't talk about him.
He'll find us.
He's not even going to be here.
Is it your uncle?
Why are you so afraid of him?
What does he do to you?
I don't know.
I used to be able to hear the doctors talking,
and they said I should have woken up.
But every time I do feel just a little bit better,
he does something, and I get sent back to a deep, dark place.
It's like the bottom of the ocean.
I almost woke up once.
That's when he moved us here.
Oh, God.
Is he here?
Yeah.
I think he's white in the waves.
Good.
Uh, I have a feeling something is going to happen.
We'll have to see it.
It won't be long.
Yes, it will.
Let's go.
Go.
Hey, it's you.
God, it's you.
Yeah.
God.
You don't believe me?
I believe you believe it, and that's enough for me.
You'll have to forgive me, Clark.
I have a personal bias against psychotherapy.
You don't like letting people in your head?
Something like that.
Well, this girl's in my head until I figure out a way to help her.
I made a few calls to Metropolis General.
It's true. Sarah was supposed to wake up.
So her uncle is drugging her.
They didn't have any evidence of foul play,
but they've only performed routine blood tests.
Maybe he's using a drug that's untraceable.
Clark, from all appearances, the guy hasn't done anything wrong.
We both know appearances can be deceiving, Lex.
Telling the cops you're hurting a dream won't get him arrested.
I appreciate your help.
Anytime.
I've always liked this sword.
What is it, some sort of legendary samurai antique?
Hardly. It's a...
It's a prop from my favorite curfew.
A Kurosawa movie.
Throne of Blood.
I bought it at auction.
Relax, Clark. It can't hurt you.
It's not real.
Right.
You've got to learn the difference between reality and fantasy.
Get some sleep.
Clark.
This is a pleasant surprise.
Thought I'd bring Sarah some fresh flowers.
Come in.
This is real nice of you, Clark.
Do you mind if I sit with her for a while?
Not at all.
Can I get you something to drink?
Anything with caffeine.
I think I might have some soda.
Anything with caffeine?
I might have some soda if anything else comes up.
Oh.
Hey侯
Hey.
I should call you-
Hello?
Hey.
When am I looking for you?
I knew you were looking for me.
You bought the right dress just now.
têm you seen me?
You can go and pick it up one day.
Sonia, what do you want?
I'm sorry to pick you up.
I'm sorry.
But me too.
Me too.
Clark?
Sarah?
He's so angry.
Wait, if you're here, it means I'm...
Hello?
Lana, hi. Come on in.
I was looking for Clark.
Brought him to pick me up.
Oh, well, he's not back from Lex's, but you're welcome to wait.
Thanks.
So you finally have new neighbors.
Yeah, not as good as the old ones.
Mrs. Kent, could I ask you something?
Of course, Lana.
Do you know why Clark pushed me away?
Metropolis changed Clark.
He's not the same boy he was when he left this spring.
Jonathan and I are trying to figure it out, too.
I guess I just, I feel like if I...
stay in his orbit long enough, he'll be fine.
I don't know.
I don't know if he'll finally decide to open up.
Martha!
Come quick, it's Clark!
Oh, my God!
Jonathan!
What happened?
I don't know, he must have fallen asleep at the wheel.
I'll call an ambulance.
No, no, Lana, I think he just hit his head.
He's gonna be fine.
Well, where was he coming from?
Lex's mansion is the other way.
Clark, I told you not to go to the Conroy's.
He was worried about Sarah.
He kept seeing her in his dreams.
This is my fault, I took him over there.
Oh, sweetie, don't blame yourself.
Clark will be fine.
What about Sarah?
I'm worried about her, too.
.
Sarah, wait!
Sarah!
We have to get away from him!
You can't keep running.
I just want to be free.
You can. In the real world.
You just have to face him.
I'm afraid.
Sarah, you're keeping us in this dream.
I can't help you until I wake up.
I have no power.
I'm sorry.
How did he know about this?
How did he know about the lilacs?
I don't know what's going on in there.
But it's gonna stop.
Don't put that needle in her.
How did you get in here?
We know you've been drugging Sarah.
Really?
Really.
You and your boyfriend are a little too neighborly for your own good.
If you kill her, there's no more money.
You said anything about killing her.
Wait.
Sarah, are you okay?
I'm all right, Clark.
She's in trouble.
Who?
Lana.
I warned you, Sarah.
This is a fight you'll never win.
Too late.
Sarah, we have to save Lana.
He's too strong. We can't stop him.
Death will follow those who trespass here.
Sarah, you have to help me.
Sarah, you cannot escape.
Return with me.
You're stronger than he is, Sarah.
You know you are.
He cannot save you.
He did this to you.
Get angry. He took six years of your life.
I control your destiny, Sarah.
Close your eyes and return to your slumber.
Don't be afraid, Sarah.
The more you resist, Sarah, the more you will suffer.
I will not let you.
I warn you again.
Clark!
Mom, Lana's in trouble.
Bonner.
Looking for this?
Lex?
What's so urgent?
I decided to do it.
Oh, do what?
Meet with the psychiatrist.
Submit to a full battery of mental tests.
Curious.
Tell me what changed your mind.
Because I was dealing from a position of fear.
If there's one thing you could sniff out like a bloodhound, it's that.
It's a gift, Lex.
And it's useful.
I'm sure you'll find it useful.
I know the only way I'm going to prove to you that I'm your rightful heir is to deal from a position of strength.
I have nothing to hide.
That would mean a lot to me, son.
I figure you're my father and you only have my best interests at heart.
Who's the good doctor?
Claire Foster.
Oh, highly credentialed.
She's published a couple of books.
She'll be able to help you work through any problems.
That island did make me crazy, Dad.
Oh, crazy? No.
Of course not.
But it'll be good to have that in writing.
Won't it?
Lex.
When you're rich, you're not crazy.
You're eccentric.
Hi, Sarah. How you doing?
Hi.
I brought you some fresh lilacs.
I know they're your favorite.
It's Clark, isn't it?
I didn't think you'd remember me.
Yeah.
We've been through so much together,
even though we've never officially met.
I still don't know how I got in your dreams.
The important thing is you're safe
and you're awake.
You're obviously a special guy.
I saw some of the things you're able to do.
Well, in our dreams, we're all super.
I just...
I know it's none of my business.
I know dreams are usually private.
No, um...
I'm curious to hear your perspective.
What'd you see?
Someone who's clearly in love.
But who resists it.
Lana, right?
Clark, take it from someone who's been trapped for six years.
If you love her that much,
don't push her away.
It's a long and complicated story, Sarah.
I only know what I saw.
I may have been there, but...
Lana's the girl you dream.
Burning the midnight oil?
I finally got some sleep.
My makeup history exam is tomorrow.
How you feeling?
Pretty stupid.
Why?
What you did was really brave.
You saved Sarah's life.
It almost cost me mine.
It's lucky you got there.
You believed in me when I thought I was losing my mind.
It was the least I could do.
So I finally met Sarah.
All she could talk about was you.
I told her I'd love to switch places.
You know, find out what goes on inside your head.
It's not that exciting.
Still. You know, maybe it would explain
why things between us.
Lana, if I had the answers up here,
you'd be the first to know.
It was just the last few days
I felt like the girl next door again.
And it was nice.
Even though it almost got you killed?
Lana,
you'll always be the girl next door.
You'll always be the girl next door.
So, um, any chance we could do something this weekend?
You know, as friends?
What'd you have in mind?
Well, it's been like an oven outside,
so I was thinking we could go swimming at Crater Lake.
I really don't think skinny dipping is a good idea.
Yeah.
Who said anything about skinny dipping?
Maybe in your dreams, Clark.
I don't know.